

Robert Park

Address: 4124 Williams Ct, Grapevine 76051, United States

Phone number: (817) 676-5346 Email address: Sahngpyo@gmail.com

Web: www.ToastyBoyProductions.com

Profile

Freelance web developer with over a year designing and implementing web applications. Proficient in creating user interfaces, troubleshooting issues, writing and testing code, and modifying websites based on user feedback. Background as a seasoned chemist, with over a decade of experience in water purification and operations, seeking to bring creativity, dedication, and enthusiasm to a web development position.

Work experience

05/2021 – present Dallas, United States

Freelance Web Developer Toasty Boy Productions

- Designed user-friendly web applications using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Wrote code for responsive web pages that display well on various devices
- **Applied** AJAX to communicate with server-side scripts and databases
- Worked with React.JS and other libraries/frameworks to create interactive web pages

04/2019 – present Dallas, United States

Shift Supervisor City of Dallas

- Generated daily shift reports for plant performance and maintenance
- Supervised operators for chemical operations and quality testing
- **Trained** new employees on company policies and operating procedures in compliance with regulatory agencies
- **Conducted** performance reviews with employees and provided feedback based on their performance

10/2016 – 04/2019 Dallas, United States

Water Treatment Plant Operator City of Dallas

- Maintained plant operations utilizing SCADA software and ensured optimal chemical feed
- Tested production water for quality assurance and compliance with regulations
- Administered training for three apprentice operators and made recommendations for performance reviews.
- Lead shift training for proper laboratory procedures and lab safety

03/2011 – 10/2016 Dallas, United States

Chemist City of Dallas

- **Developed** models for more efficient dosages of treatment chemicals, resulting in a 7% reduction in chemical expenditure
- **Programmed** a chemical inventory monitoring system to prevent depleted inventory situations
- **Evaluated** new chemists for proficiency and accuracy in chemical analyses and proper data management
- **Implemented** an innovative and more efficient method for lime analysis and incorporated new instrumentation to reduce testing time by 30%

Education

2016 – 2018 Dallas, United States Master | Business Administration Southern Methodist University 2006 – 2010 Waco, United States

Bachelor of Science | Chemistry Baylor University

Skills

- WEB DEVELOPMENT

HTML5/CSS3 JavaScript

React.JS Node.JS

Figma PHP

Python MySQL

Git GitHub

SQL Agile

Bootstrap SASS

npm jQuery

TypeScript ES6